Okay, another thing that for me is important.
It may not be for you.
But for me I use very strong chemicals.
Some people may prefer to use products that don't have chemicals.
But because I do, I enjoy having the disinfectants.
I like to wear a mask while I'm cleaning.
Because you don't need to be breathing those chemicals in.
Especially you know when, I'm pregnant.
A lot of women, a lot of you out there.
And men too that clean bathrooms.
Feel free to get the.
You have little masks, they're just paper masks.
You can get them at Home Depot or Lowes.
And they're actually called painters masks.
Some of them are just made of paper.
But they're very affordable.
You can get a pack of, you know, several for just a couple of dollars.
So make sure you.
If you have those, keep them in here on hand.
You know, it protects your health when you're cleaning.
You don't have to worry about any hazardous chemical getting into your system.
And it just makes the whole process a lot safer for you.
And for your children if you have children that help out cleaning around the house.
So I would recommend having a mask on hand.